{"html":[{"type":"mc","question":"What does HTML stand for?","c1":"Hypertext Markup Language","c2":"Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language","c3":"Head Text Marked Language","c4":"Hypertext Modified Language","correct":"c1","fb":"All the other acronyms do not exist, it is a markup language."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the largest heading in HTML?","c1":"<h6>","c2":"<h1>","c3":"<heading>","c4":"head","fb":"Headings range from <h1> to <h6> the lower the number the more important the heading."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which tag is used to create an ordered list?","c1":"<ol>","c2":"<ul>","c3":"<li>","c4":"<a>","fb":"<ol> stands for ordered list, <ul> is unordered list and <li> is used to list the items."},
  {"type":"textResponse","question":"Type in below the correct tag for creating a hyperlink","correct":"<a>","fb":"<a> is the main way to define a hyperlink."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the correct way to create a table","c1":"<td>","c2":"<t>","c3":"<table>","c4":"<tr>","correct":"c3","fb":"<table> is the way to initiate a table and <t> is not a tag that exist. <td> is used to enter table data and <tr> is to define rows in the table."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which tag is used for adding videos to a website?","c1":"<video>","c2":"<media>","c3":"<vid>","c4":"<movie>","correct":"c1","fb":"This was tricky, but <media>, <movie>, and <vid> doesn't exist as a tag."},
  {"type":"textResponse","question":"How is a HTML5 document initialized?","correct":"<!DOCTYPE html>","fb":"Other tags like <html> is used to start a HTML file, but to initialize the entire document use <!DOCTYPE html>"},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which tag is used for adding sound to a website?","c1":"<sound>","c2":"<media>","c3":"<audio>","c4":"<mp3>","correct":"c3","fb":"<media>, <sound>, <mp3> all doesn't exist."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the correct way to make the text bold?","c1":"<imp>","c2":"<bold>","c3":"<em>","c4":"<b>","correct":"<b>","fb":"<b> stands for bold, but <bold> is not a tag, while <em> is used to italicize words and <imp> doesn't exist."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What character is used to close a tag?","c1":"/","c2":"*","c3":"+","c4":"-","correct":"c1","fb":"Use / to close a tag."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What HTML element is used to inserting a line break?","c1":"<break>","c2":"<br>","c3":"<brake>","c4":"<line>","correct":"c2","fb": "<br> is short for break."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the HTML element used for creating a bullet list?","c1":"<list>","c2":"<bl>","c3":"<ul>","c4":"<ol>","correct":"c3","fb":"<ul> is an unordered list whereas <ol> is an ordered list."},
  {"type":"tc","question":"What HTML attribute is used to define inline-styles directly on HTML element?","correct":"style","fb":"Only use style to define styles in a HTML file."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"How can you add a comment in HTML?","c1":"<!-- and -->","c2":"//","c3":"/*","c4":"comment","correct":"c1","fb":"<!-- and --> is the correct way to leave a comment on HTML, // and /* is for Java."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Select the correct way to create a checkbox field.","c1":"<input type=\"checkbox\">","c2":"<input style=\"checkbox\">","c3":"<input style=\"check\">","c4":"<checkbox>","correct":"c1","fb":"<input type=\"checkbox\"> is the correct way to create a checkbox field while the other choices does not exist."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"How many different headings are there?","c1":"1","c2":"6","c3":"3","c4":"4","correct":"c2","fb": "Headings range from <h1> to <h6>."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Select the correct HTML syntax for creating a text input.","c1":"<input type=\"text\">","c2":"<textfield>","c3":"<input type=\"textfield\">","c4":"<input style=\"text\">","correct":"c1","fb":"No need to put all the extra words as shown in the other choices just \"text\"."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which is the correct way to set a background color for the HTML page?","c1":"<body bg='yellow'>","c2":"<body style=\"background-color:blue\">","c3":"<background setColor:red>","c4":"<body background-color=green>","correct":"c2","fb":"style = background-color is the correct way to set a background color for the HTML page."},
  {"type":"textResponse","question":"Enter below the correct tag to use when implementing JavaScript in HTML.","correct":"<script>","fb":"<script is correct way to implement JavaScript in the HTML file."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which is the correct way to put a picture on the HTML page?","c1":"<media>","c2":"<image>","c3":"<pic>","c4":"<img>","correct":"c4","fb":"<img> is the only one that exists in HTML."}],
  "java":[{"type":"textResponse","question":"Type in the correct method to output something in Java?","correct":"println()","fb":"println() displays the things that you are trying to print."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the correct data type to store text?","c1":"String","c2":"string","c3":"str","c4":"Text","correct":"c1","fb":"String is the correct way, make sure it the 'S' is capitalized. The uncapitlize is used in C++. str is python and text is not used in Java."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which is the correct way to declare an array?","c1":"<>","c2":"()","c3":"{}","c4":"[]","correct":"c4","fb":"Arrays are declared with '[]', '()' are used in methods and '{}' are used for classes."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which variable is used to store integers (whole numbers)?","c1":"float","c2":"int","c3":"String","c4":"boolean","correct":"c2","fb":"int is used for integers, float is used for decimals, and String is used for collection of characters. Boolean is used for t (true) or f (false)."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is another way of writing the notation x=x+2","c1":"y=x-2","c2":"x=y-2","c3":"x+=2","c4":"x-=2","correct":"c3","fb":"+= is used to add the variable with the value while have the return store as the variable."},
  {"type":"textResponse","question":"What keyword is used to return a value in a method?","correct":"return","fb":"return is used in a method to return the value."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which is used to stop a loop?","c1":"exit","c2":"stop","c3":"break","c4":"return","correct":"c3","fb":"break implements a stop to the loop."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is import used for?","c1":"To import a package from Java API library","c2":"To import a method","c3":"To import a variable","c4":"To import an array","correct":"c1","fb":"import is used to access the Java API library and import it into the java file."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What operator is used to compare two numeric values?","c1":">","c2":"=","c3":"==","c4":"<","correct":"c3","fb":"== is used to compare two numeric values."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What method is used to find the size of a String?","c1":"length()","c2":"getLength()","c3":"size()","c4":"getSize()","correct":"c1","fb":"length() is used to return the size of the String."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the method .equals() used for?","c1":"Compare String variables.","c2":"To set a String to a variable","c3":"To compare two operators","c4":"To compare packages.","correct":"c1","fb": ".equals() is used to compare two String instances."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What operator is used to add two values together?","c1":"-","c2":"+","c3":"*","c4":"<","correct":"c2","fb":"+ is used to add."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?","c1":"toUpperCase()","c2":"upperCase()","c3":"touppercase()","c4":"capitalize()","correct":"c1","fb": "toUpperCase() is the only valid method in Java."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Array indexes start with","c1":"1","c2":"0","c3":"10","c4":"2","correct":"c2","fb":"Array start at position 0 due to the off by one error."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the correct way to create a method?","c1":"(name)","c2":"name[]","c3":"name()","c4":"<name>","correct":"c3","fb":"name() is the correct way to create a method, methodName[] would be an array and the other two doesn't exist."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What operator is used to end each line of code?","c1":"<","c2":"/","c3":">","c4":";","correct":"c4","fb":"; closes out each line of code."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of myClass?","c1":"myClass myObj=new myClass();","c2":"class myClass=new myObject;","c3":"new myObj=myClass();","c4":"class myObj=new myClass();","correct":"c1","fb":"The class goes first then object name and then call the class."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which method can be used to find the highest value between x and y?","c1":"Math.maxNum(x,y)","c2":"Math.max(x,y)","c3":"Math.largest(x,y)","c4":"Math.maximum(x,y)","correct":"c2","fb":"Math.max() is the correct method that is part of the default java library."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which operator is used to multiple numbers?","c1":"x","c2":"+","c3":"*","c4":"/","correct":"c3","fb":"* is used to multiple numbers in Java not the traditional x."},
  {"type":"mc","question":"Which keyword keeps the main method from returning any value?","c1":"restricted","c2":"concealed","c3":"void","c4":"null","correct":"c3","fb":"void is the only one that works in this case."}
  ]}
